{"instructions": ["This section is an extended version of the previous task, which is clicking on <strong>first</strong> or <strong>second</strong> to indicate which sound beep has fluctuation. <p></p>In cases where you can not tell the fluctuation, just give your best guess.", "When you are ready, click <strong>Continue</strong> to hear the first two sound beeps"], "feedback": true, "holdfeedback": false, "feedbackdur": 600, "serveraudio": false, "estimatedduration": 4, "randomize": false, "isi": 600, "volume": [{"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "To begin, please use the same volume as in the previous task<p> Click <strong>Continue</strong> to proceed.</p>", "choices": ["Continue"]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "Is the right headphone in your right ear, and the left headphone in your left ear? It is very important!", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue."]}], "trials": [{"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/1.6Hz_1_qBMHx2syGdohg3c0.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "1.6Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.4Hz_1_ELf8OC1qZu6p7FJ9.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.4Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/3.2Hz_1_dcYzxG3zLfuipxqn.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.2Hz_2_m3UH8Jn11tu0EdWA.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/1.6Hz_1_wXcT2rOoMe7Lxb1L.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "1.6Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.1Hz_2_a4zTjY4WUzRJKvRj.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.1Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/3.2Hz_2_HIR564L5hvcHTlAg.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.1Hz_2_HVN3dkzT3biAVGUk.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.1Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.4Hz_2_aT9hwlSl9bcX1JUG.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.4Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/3.2Hz_1_FdduN3PQRXOGu5pF.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.2Hz_1_0H4v55Kgwrqoa3CJ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.2Hz_2_97PTuGqSWfnmMSZb.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.2Hz_1_xvdVyPIdt75xMIZ7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/1.6Hz_2_ImnRKK8KgkgjPNxk.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "1.6Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/1.6Hz_2_yUsN2mDhideMzN1V.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "1.6Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.2Hz_2_6TpSQVUtFVJ7k4Ur.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.8Hz_1_iI8BKgmkcqowi9Fy.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.8Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.1Hz_1_y5ELaKWOGZ7tXraf.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.1Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.8Hz_1_bkBVQSC495C4xLI0.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.8Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/1.6Hz_2_LOtulgrvH9bR41h7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "1.6Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.4Hz_2_1wN1bexjcWuYkP2U.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.4Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/3.2Hz_1_wqufBCbNdkQIarxj.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.4Hz_1_wZHYCaakwSjrNrtj.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.4Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.4Hz_2_3yPp6MmgJrejdQWY.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.4Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.1Hz_2_LavHMBYi8ZvMsfGZ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.1Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.8Hz_2_uyjuIIjhyZlFh1VI.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.8Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.2Hz_1_24EG4JWPDnLlm1hO.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.8Hz_2_TscZwP3q9ZXOHxYK.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.8Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.4Hz_2_W0E2umEbZqQXQOoD.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.4Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/1.6Hz_1_mqWuLlfto46bKcAG.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "1.6Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.4Hz_2_p4VI3wuMfxlYSP4Y.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.4Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.2Hz_1_fF7058xtWn75wvQS.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.4Hz_2_gIcUOLoSSvc0VFRX.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.4Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/3.2Hz_2_Jrq3wj6O8mZEKcIN.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/1.6Hz_1_Fd0KQOM7kD0EVlQ4.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "1.6Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.8Hz_1_cnP2vb4D4uQbFuu7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.8Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/3.2Hz_1_NzJ7MjZTgksAGrZX.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.1Hz_2_gPvPsQyymSY5FlLm.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.1Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/3.2Hz_2_A5xRKgz5dxoow5FX.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/1.6Hz_1_6ieR5gOjRMcX9Bvd.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "1.6Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.1Hz_2_LpOd6fuOFGxVrO5u.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.1Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.8Hz_2_hjzQOQahV0U65nFW.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.8Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.2Hz_2_ITdEouIUzFhnsBoq.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.1Hz_2_6MpgHBQVyJm6Fro7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.1Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.8Hz_2_OWJF2ypr4R0xNb5D.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.8Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.1Hz_2_uMutOAgo8ROubJcq.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.1Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/0.8Hz_1_VMtsekSf4AeJZvWR.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"fdev": "0.8Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/main/3.2Hz_1_yAAnEcJd21u879ja.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}]}